<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>1 | Lehrstuhl Maschinelles Lernen</title><link>https://example.com/publications-type/1/</link><atom:link href="https://example.com/publications-type/1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>1</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://example.com/media/logo_hueebd31b28f82aeb63357b594dab7cdfb_24654_300x300_fit_lanczos_3.png</url><title>1</title><link>https://example.com/publications-type/1/</link></image><item><title>FLAIR: An Easy-to-Use Framework for State-of-the-Art NLP</title><link>https://example.com/publications/2019-flair-framework/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/publications/2019-flair-framework/</guid><description>&lt;p>We present FLAIR, an NLP framework designed to facilitate training and distribution of state-of-the-art sequence labeling, text classification and language models. The core idea of the framework is to present a simple, unified interface for conceptually very different types of word and document embeddings. This effectively hides all embedding-specific engineering complexity and allows researchers to “mix and match” various embeddings with little effort. The framework also implements standard model training and hyperparameter selection routines, as well as a data fetching module that can download publicly available NLP datasets and convert them into data structures for quick set up of experiments. Finally, FLAIR also ships with a “model zoo” of pre-trained models to allow researchers to use state-of-the-art NLP models in their applications. This paper gives an overview of the framework and its functionality. The framework is available on GitHub at &lt;a href="https://github.com/flairNLP/flair" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://github.com/flairNLP/flair&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>